everyday.com.my 2012-01-09

# One-Stop Search For Warehouse Sales, Clearance Sales, Sales Voucher & Hidden Promotion in Malaysia - Everyday.com.my

**Scope**

This privacy policy describes how we handle your personal information for our services available through the www.everyday.com.my (the "Site") and applies generally to our subsidiaries and joint venture web sites whose specific privacy policies are available from our Privacy Central pages. Our subsidiaries and joint ventures privacy practices are similar to those described in this Privacy Policy. Subject to the requirements of applicable law, we strive to provide a consistent set of privacy practices throughout the global Everyday.com.my exchange community. By accepting the Privacy Policy and the User Agreement in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective on 1st January 2008. 

**Collection**

You can browse the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. Once you give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us. If you choose to provide us with personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of that information to our servers located in the Malaysia & United States. 

We may collect and store the following personal information: 

  * email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information, such as credit card or bank account numbers: 
  * transactional information based on your activities on the Site. 
  * community discussions, chats, dispute resolution, correspondence through the Site, and correspondence sent to us: 
  * computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Site, and ad data: 
  * other information, including IP address and standard web log information: and 
  * supplemental information from third parties. 

**Marketing**

We don't sell or rent your personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect from other companies (such as demographic data) to improve and personalize our services. If you don't wish to receive marketing communications from us, simply indicate your preference once you sign-in on the Site. 

**Use**

Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to: 

  * provide the services and customer support you request; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our User Agreement; 
  * customize, measure, and improve our services and the Site's content and layout; 
  * tell you about targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers based on your communication preferences; and 
  * compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties. 

**Our Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. 

We may also share your personal information with: 

  * service providers under contract who help with our business operations; (such as fraud investigations, bill collection, affiliate and rewards programs and co-branded credit cards) 
  * other third parties to whom you explicitly ask us to send your information; (or about whom you are otherwise explicitly notified and consent to when using a specific service) 
  * law enforcement or other governmental officials, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity; (In such events we will disclose name, city, state, telephone number, email address, User ID history, fraud complaints, and bidding and listing history.) 
  * other business entities, should we plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. (Should such a combination occur, we will require that the new combined entity follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information. If your personal information will be used contrary to this policy, you will receive prior notice.) 

Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity. 

**Activity Associated with Username**

Your Username is displayed throughout the Site and is therefore available to the public. All of your activities on the Site will be traceable to your Username. Therefore, if you associate your name with your username, the people to whom you have revealed your name to will be able to personally identify your Everyday.com.my activities. 

**Cookies**

We use "cookies" (small files placed on your hard drive) on certain pages of the Site to help analyze our web page flow, customize our services, measure promotional effectiveness, and promote trust and safety. 

A few important things you should know about cookies are that: 

  * We offer certain features that are only available through the use of cookies. 
  * We use cookies to help identify you and maintain your signed-in status. 
  * Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted from your hard drive at the end of a session. 
  * You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits, although doing so may interfere with your use of the Site. 
  * You may encounter cookies from third parties on certain pages of the Site that we do not control. (For example, if you view a web page created by another user, there may be a "cookie" placed by that web page.). 

**No Spam, Spyware or Cookies**

We and our users do not tolerate spam. Make sure to set your Everyday.com.my notification preferences so we communicate to you as you prefer. To report Everyday.com.my related spam or spoof emails to Everyday.com.my, please forward the email to support@everyday.com.my. You may not use our communication tools to send spam or otherwise send content that would violate our User Agreement. We do filter and automatically scan messages before they are sent for viruses and other illegal or prohibited content but do not permanently store email messages sent through these tools. If you send an email to an email address that is not registered in our community (via Refer a Friend or other tool), we do not permanently store that email or use that email address for any marketing purpose. We do not rent or sell these email addresses. 

**Account Protection**

Your password is the key to your account. Use unique numbers, letters, and special characters and do not disclose your Everyday.com.my password to anyone. If you do share your password or your personal information with others, remember that you are responsible for all actions taken in the name of your account. If you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personal information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately notify Everyday.com.my and change your password. 

**Accessing, Reviewing and Changing Your Personal Information**

You can see, review and change most of your personal information by logging into the Site. Generally, we will not manually modify your personal information because it is very difficult to verify your identity remotely. You must promptly update your personal information if it changes or is inaccurate. Once you make a public posting, you may not be able to change or remove it. Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts in order to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Everyday.com.my User Agreement, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law. 

**Security**

Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset that must be protected and use lots of tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know, third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the Site. Therefore, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. 

**Third Parties**

Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others, whether they are bidders, buyers, or sellers on our Site or other sites throughout the Internet, different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. Since Everyday.com.my does not control the privacy policies of third parties, you are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your personal information to others. 

**E-Mail And E-Mail Addresses**

If you were to subscribe any promotional emails from [Everyday.com.my](http://www.everyday.com.my/), we will collect your e-mail address We may use and display your full name and email address when you send an email notification to a friend through [Everyday.com.my](http://www.everyday.com.my/) (such as in an invitation, or when sharing your content). Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of your friends (such as when someone sends you a personal message) or notifications from a social network or other website with whom you have registered to receive such notifications. We may use this e-mail address to contact you, for things such as notifications of limited edition shop sales and other related information. You may indicate your preference to stop receiving further promotional communications as further detailed below. 

Besides sending promotional emails, Everyday.com.my will also send you  
\- Application process, services, enquiries or feedback  
\- Service surveys  
\- Billings or payments  
\- Public notices 

**Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information**

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly at [support@everyday.com.my](mailto:support@everyday.com.my). 

If you would like to contact us for further details, we are contactable at: 

Intergrated Methods Sdn Bhd  
Lot 55-6 The Boulevard,  
Mid Valley City, Lingkaran Syed Putra  
59200 Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia  
Tel: 03 228 34599  
support@everyday.com.my

**General**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on the Site. All amended terms automatically take effect 30 days after they are initially posted on the Site. In addition, we will notify you in accordance with your Notification Preferences.
